Farewell, Earth
The ship that is departing is
The Space Battleship
Yamato
It departs now to Iscandar,
at the end of the cosmos,
bearing its fate.
"We will come back, no matter what it takes"
Answer with a smile to the waving people
Going far from the Galaxy towards Iscandar
A faint gleam of hope
The Space Battleship Yamato
Welcome back
Welcome home, Yurisha.
And you, as well, Sasha.
No, this is...
Mori Yuki...
She is an Earthling.
Rud Iscandar.
Eiji Ishizu
Mamoru Kodai
Irun Yurisha
Episode 24
The Distant Promised Land
This star is the only one
If you look for something so beautiful
It is not something you can see
You will find it inside anyone
Love is the answer
Sorrow and strife
May cloud the blue sky
The overlapping warmth
Becomes a light to illuminate the world
A wish to the infinite universe
All is forgiven
And we all laugh together
Not a trick of the eye
But a dream from the bottom of my heart
No matter what tomorrow brings
Walk on
If you have nothing special
Only the strength to yearn for it
Bound to the limits of time
Create the trace of a miracle
A wish to the infinite universe
All is forgiven
And we all laugh together
Not a trick of the eye
A dream from the bottom of my heart
No matter what tomorrow brings
Walk on
Together with you
Forever